Previously on SEAL Team...
之前在海豹突击队......
My integrated deterrence partnership has been approved.
我的综合威慑 合作关系已获批准。
You ready for your new role at DEVGRU?
你准备好 DEVGRU 的新角色？
I won't let you down, sir.
我不会让您失望的，先生。
Do you remember Ben,
你还记得本吗？
the vet that Clay was trying to help?
Clay 的兽医 正在尝试帮忙吗？
Ben pled to, uh, felony vandalism.
本承诺，呃， 重罪破坏行为。
Stella is gonna show up and ask for leniency.
Stella 会出现 并请求宽大处理。
She asked if I would go with her.
她问我 会和她一起去。
The job's changing,
工作在变化，
op tempo with it.
与之同步。
If you've conquered all the demons
如果你已经征服 所有的恶魔 十三
war made you endure, then Brad can, too.
战争使你忍耐， 那么布拉德也可以。
That public temper tantrum that you threw
公众脾气 你发脾气
didn't win you many hearts and minds.
没有赢得你很多 心灵。
I would just like to know why my teammates
我只是想 知道为什么我的队友
are suffering for my actions.
因我的行为而受苦。
15 years as an exemplary SEAL,
15 年来作为模范海豹突击队员，
and I end up in Command's doghouse.
我最终 指挥部的狗窝。
- Not sure you all have met. - Drew Franklin.
- 不确定你们都见过。 - 德鲁·富兰克林。
- Thought he was an urban legend. - You're all here for an assignment.
——以为他是一个都市传说。 - 你们来这里是为了完成一项任务。
You all will be spending the next month
你们都会 下个月的支出
working with Swedish SOG.
与瑞典SOG合作。
No, he can't boss me because he's not my boss.
不，他不能指挥我 因为他不是我的老板。 二十五
He's Bravo 1, and he outranks all of us.
他是 Bravo 1，他 比我们所有人都高。 二十六
- Ah, this isn't an op. - Relax, dude.
- 啊，这不是手术。 - 放松，兄弟。 二十七
It's detention.
这是拘留。 二十八
We got active shooters in the mall.
我们变得活跃起来 商场里的枪手。 二十九
This is a coordinated attack.
这是一次有组织的攻击。 三十
We got no weapons between us to take 'em out.
我们之间没有武器 我们来把他们消灭掉。
Shitbirds inside are using civilians for target practice.
里面的 Shitbirds 正在使用 平民进行射击练习。 三十二
Bombs and shooters?
炸弹和射手？
This is more than a lone wolf attack.
这不仅仅是 孤狼式的进攻。 三十四
So who's doing it?
那么是谁在做这件事？ 三十五
- Feels like Mumbai or Beslan. - All that matters is,
- 感觉像孟买或别斯兰。 - 重要的是， 三十六
whoever they are, they get put down hard.
无论他们是谁，他们 受到严厉打击。 三十七
- Where's a SAW when you need one? - All right, look.
当你需要电锯时它在哪儿？ - 好的，你看。 三十八
Being unarmed, that doesn't make us helpless.
由于手无寸铁， 不会让我们无助。 三十九
Ray, Omar, stay here, triage the wounded.
雷，奥马尔，留在这里， 对伤员进行分类救治。
- We'll do what we can, boss. - All right, Brock,
- 老板，我们会尽力的。 - 好吧，布洛克，
Sonny, Drew, with me inside the mall.
桑尼、德鲁和 我在商场里。 四十二
We're gonna help whoever we can however we can, got it?
我们会帮助任何我们 但是我们可以，明白了吗？
First responders are gonna need intel when they arrive.
急救人员将 到达时需要情报。 四十四
Save 'em some time if you can get the shooters'
节省一些时间 你可以得到射手的 四十五
- numbers and locations. - All right, look.
- 数字和位置。 - 好的，你看。 四十六
Without comms, we use cell phones to communicate.
没有通讯，我们使用手机 手机进行通讯。 四十七
You better AirDrop those Bat Phone digits there,
你最好用 AirDrop 发送这些 那里有蝙蝠电话号码， 四十八
Drewce Wayne.
德鲁斯·韦恩。
Okay.
好的。
Got it. You solid?
明白了。你确定吗？
- Let's move. - Jace.
- 我们走吧。 — 杰斯。
You sure you don't want me or Omar inside instead of Drew?
你确定你不想要我或者 里面是奥马尔而不是德鲁？
Guy's a total wild card.
这家伙真是个难以捉摸的人。
That's exactly why I want him on my hip,
这就是为什么我 想要他靠在我腰上，
so I can manage him, all right?
这样我就能管理他了，可以吗？
Roger that.
收到。
Move. Get to your right.
动。往你的右边走。
I've got an unknown over here.
我这里有一个未知数。
Sonny, Brock, bump up.
桑尼、布洛克，快上来。
See if you can get eyes on the shooter.
看看你是否能得到 眼睛盯着射手。
Okay, easy. Help him out.
好的，很简单。帮帮他吧。
Come on.
快点。
- Anything? - The lights are on
- 任何事物？ - 灯亮着
but nobody's answering.
但没人回答。
- Should we exfil him? - Nah, the people deeper inside
- 我们应该把他撤离吗？ - 不，内心深处的人
the mall are more in danger.
商场的危险性更大。
Let's try and get him up. Go easy.
让我们尝试一下 把他抱起来。放轻松。
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Over here.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。过来。
Help us out with this guy.
帮帮我们解决这个家伙。
We got to get him out now.
我们现在必须把他救出来。
Easy on his leg. All right?
轻点他的腿。好吗？
Go to your right. Okay, move, move.
往你的右边走。 好啦，动起来，动起来。
Sounds like the good guys with guns are coming.
听起来像好人 带着枪来了。
It's about fucking time.
他妈的是时候了。
Sonny?
桑尼？
I got eyes on three of these assholes.
我看到了三个 这些混蛋。
They got AKs, chest rigs and sidearms.
他们有 AK，胸膛 钻机和随身武器。
Is that all of them?
就这些吗？
Think there's a fourth. Haven't seen him yet,
认为还有第四个。 还没见过他，
but I can definitely hear his gun.
但我肯定可以 听到他的枪。
It's carnage, Jace.
这是一场大屠杀，杰斯。
We just got to keep doing what we're doing till the cops
我们只需继续努力 警察来之前我们做什么
storm this fucking place with guns a-blazing.
冲进这个鬼地方 枪炮齐鸣。
Get down!
下来！
Folks are Swedish fish in a barrel.
瑞典人 瓮中之鳖。
We can't just watch them get mowed down.
我们不能只是观看 他们被击倒了。
It's a good thing this guy can't hit
这是一件好事 这家伙打不中
- two targets at the same time. - Playing decoy
- 同时攻击两个目标。 - 扮演诱饵
without our kit ain't a good idea, Jace.
没有我们的装备 好主意，杰斯。
I've got this, old-timers.
我明白了，老前辈们。
Easy, all right?
简单点，可以吗？
Save that speed for the civilians.
保存速度 对于平民来说。
When I move, you move.
我动，你也动。
Come on!
快点！
Go, go, go!
去！去！去！
Down the stairs, let's go.
下楼梯吧，我们走吧。
Copy that, 1.
复制，1。
I'll relay that info.
我会传达该信息。
Hey.
嘿。
I'm going to give the police an intel dump from Jason.
我要报警 来自杰森的情报转储。
- You good? - Solid. Go.
- 你还好吗？ - 稳住。出发。
- All right. - All right, let's see here.
- 好的。 - 好的，我们来看看。
Oh, oh...
噢，噢……
Uh...
呃…
Oh, oh. I'm an American, I'm here to help.
哦，哦。我是美国人， 我来帮忙。
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么？
I'm U.S. military, here on a training exercise.
我是美国军人，在这里 在一次训练演习中。
Four of my teammates are inside helping to evacuate people.
我的四个队友在里面 协助撤离人员。
When are you moving in?
你什么时候搬进来？
Ambulance and paramedics are on their way.
救护车和护理人员 正在路上。
What about the shooters?
那么射手们又如何呢？
You need to assault. People are dying.
你需要进攻。 人们正在死去。
Talk to me, Ray.
跟我说话，雷。
Yeah, the police are here, but they're holding
是的，警察 这里，但他们正在持有
for their tactical team to show up.
他们的战术 团队出现。
Fuck SWAT. Fucking clown show.
操他妈的特警。操他妈的小丑表演。
Yeah.
是的。
Nobody's moving in?
没人搬进来吗？
Waiting for the goddamn tactical team.
等待 该死的战术小组。
That could take hours.
这可能需要几个小时。
You remember Nairobi?
你还记得内罗毕吗？
These people don't got time, Jace.
这些人没有 有时间，杰斯。
Yeah, we're the only motherfuckers here
是的，我们是唯一 混蛋在这里
who can do anything.
他无所不能。
Time to go on the offensive.
是时候发起进攻了。
Four guys with AKs against four guys with cell phones
四个手持 AK 的男子对战 四个拿着手机的人
isn't a fair fight, almighty Bravo or not.
这不是一场公平的战斗， 无论是否是全能的 Bravo。
Nancy Drew already solved this case.
南希朱尔已经 解决了这个案子。
Our arsenal is as thin as a fiddle string.
我们的武器库很薄弱 像小提琴弦一样。
My grandninny always taught me not
我的孙女 总是教导我不要
to dig up more snakes than I could kill.
挖出更多蛇 比我能杀死的人还多。
Slow is smooth, smooth is fast.
慢即是顺，顺即是快。
One step at a time.
一步一步来。
- Yeah, what's step one? - Get a gun.
- 是的，第一步是什么？ - 拿把枪。
What have you got?
你有什么？
Broken femur. Makeshift splint isn't much help.
股骨骨折。临时措施 夹板没有太大帮助。
We need to stabilize it.
我们需要使其稳定下来。
The ambulance should be here soon.
救护车 应该很快就到了。
It's got to be her femoral artery.
一定是她 股动脉。
Broken bone must've cut it.
骨头断裂了，肯定是割伤了。
All right, look, we need
好的，看，我们需要
to rig up a pressure dressing to buy us some time.
制造压力 穿衣打扮，为我们争取一些时间。
Samara...
萨马拉……
Hey, look, grab me that baby bottle.
嘿，看，抓住我 那个婴儿奶瓶。
Thinking the lid
思考盖子
- will make a plug for the artery? - I'm gonna try.
- 会堵塞动脉吗？ - 我会尝试的。
It won't hold long.
它不会持续太久。
What, are you worried about her lungs?
怎么，你担心吗 她的肺怎么样？
Blast wave injuries are tricky
爆炸波造成的伤害很棘手
without that X-ray vision.
没有那种X射线视野。
Oh, God, this isn't working.
噢，天哪，这不管用。
Hey.
嘿。
Let me, uh...
让我，呃…
let me see if the cops
让我看看警察
have a trauma kit with a proper tourniquet, okay?
准备一个带有 合适的止血带，好吗？
All right, but what about the girl? She okay?
好吧，但是 那女孩怎么样？她还好吗？
Keep an eye on her.
留意她。
Looks like we found our rifle, boys.
看来我们找到了 我们的步枪，孩子们。
We're getting sucked into the room.
我们被坑了 進入房間。
Brock, how long will it take for Pepper
布洛克，还要多久 Pepper 需要
to get on the bite from here?
从这里开始咬钩？
About five seconds or so.
大概五秒钟左右。
About three fewer seconds
大约少了三秒
than it takes to reload an AK.
比重新装填 AK 所需的时间还长。
As soon as he goes dry, you send him.
他一走 干，你送他去。
We're gonna need to be on him fast.
我们需要 快点追上他。
Follow the dog.
跟着狗。
- Dead nuts sprint. - Fuck yeah.
- 疯狂冲刺。 - 操啊。
Pepper...
胡椒...
50 grand of dog training finally pays off, right?
50 万美元的狗训练费 最终还是会有回报吧？
I got dibs on the big gun.
我得到了这把大枪。
Jackpot. Now we can finally get in these psychos' game plan.
大奖。现在我们终于可以得到 在这些精神病患者的游戏计划中。
Yeah, if only any of us spoke Swedish.
是的，如果有的话 我们所有人都说瑞典语。
Hey.
嘿。
Over here. Come here.
过来。过来。
You speak English?
你会说英语吗？
Ja.
是的。
This is what I want you to do, I want you to head that way,
这就是我要你做的， 我希望你朝那个方向走，
back to the main entrance. It's all clear there.
回到正门。 那里一切都清楚。
Give this to the police. You understand?
把这个交给 警察。你明白吗？
Good.
好的。
All right, look, we got two teams.
好吧，你看， 我们有两支队伍。
Me and Drew with the Glock,
我和德鲁拿着格洛克手枪，
Sonny, Brock, the AK.
桑尼、布洛克、AK。
- Got it? - We got three guys that are still vertical.
- 知道了？ - 我们有三个人仍然垂直。
What's the plan, Jace?
有什么计划吗，杰斯？
Straight hunter killer.
直率的猎人杀手。
Put them down and end this.
放下他们并结束这一切。
Straight up. Sonny, head east.
一直往上走。儿子，往东走。
- We got west. Let's roll. - Let's go make that Navy money.
- 我们到西边了。出发吧。 - 让我们去赚海军的钱吧。
Samara?
萨马拉？
Samara!
萨马拉！
Help her, please.
请帮助她。
Please! Please...
拜托！拜托……
If the plug comes out of your leg,
如果插头 从你的腿上，
you'll die.
你会死的。
You're too weak to hold it.
你太虚弱了，拿不住它。
If she dies, I have no reason to live.
如果她死了，我 没有活下去的理由。
Please, I can manage.
拜托，我能应付。
If you save her, you'll have saved me, too.
如果你救了她，你就会 也救了我。
Please. Please!
拜托了。拜托了！
All right, just-just, just keep holding tight.
好吧，只是，只是， 继续坚持。
All right, I'm gonna relieve the pressure
好的，我要 缓解压力
that's built up in her chest cavity.
这是建立在 她的胸腔。
Let's move.
我们走吧。
What's Swedish for Mexican standoff?
瑞典语是什么意思 墨西哥僵局？
Sure could use that rifle right now.
当然可以用它 现在就用步枪。
Can Pepper fetch as good as she takes a shit?
Pepper 能否取得同样好的成绩 当她拉屎的时候？
Not a chance.
没机会。
Right, left. Right, right, right, left.
右，左。右， 右，右，左。
Hey.
嘿。
- Please... - Where you hurt?
- 请... - 你哪里受伤了？
My leg. They shot me.
我的腿。他们向我开枪。
That's a lot of blood.
流了好多血啊。
We'll need to get him back to the CCP.
我们需要 让他回归中国共产党。
I can't leave.
我不能离开。
I sent my children inside that store to hide.
我让我的孩子们进去 那家商店隐藏起来。
Slow down, all right? You're no good to 'em out here like this,
慢点，好吗？你不是 对他们这样好，
you understand me?
你明白我的意思？
I promise I'll get your kids
我保证会救你的孩子
back to you safe.
平安回到你身边。
- Here. - No, no, no, you take it.
- 这里。 - 不不不，你拿着。
There could be more enemy back there where we cleared before.
可能会有更多敌人回来 那里是我们之前清理过的地方。
You understand? Plus he's gonna slow you down.
你明白了吗？另外 他会让你慢下来。
Let's get him up.
我们把他扶起来吧。
- Okay. - Got it?
- 好的。 - 知道了？
Got him?
抓到他了？
- Hey, keep your head on a swivel. - I got you.
- 嘿，保持头脑清醒。 - 我接到你了。
I got two mags left.
我还剩下两本杂志。
Nothing's gonna change unless something changes.
什么都不会改变 除非情况发生变化。
Then we got to flank him.
然后我们从侧翼进攻他。
That's gonna be awful hard with one weapon.
那会很糟糕 用一件武器就能完成。
He's got to think he's being flanked on both sides, okay?
他肯定认为自己 两边都有，可以吗？
- Here, take this. - Okay.
- 来，拿着这个。 - 好的。
Time to shine, Pepper. Let's go, baby.
闪耀光芒的时刻到了，佩珀。 走吧，宝贝。
Set. Set, set.
设定。设定，设定。
Pepper!
胡椒！
That's three down.
已经有三个了。
Make sure you grab his rifle.
确保你抓住他的步枪。
How do you not have one single trauma kit?
你怎么没有 一套创伤急救包吗？
You got a woman fighting for her life over there.
你有一个女人在打架 她在那里的生活。
Look, if you won't do something for the people inside,
听着，如果你不做点什么 对于里面的人来说，
at least do something for the people out here.
至少做点什么 对这里的人们来说
What?
什么？
What is it?
它是什么？
Go.
去。
That radio you grabbed was a gold mine.
你抢到的那台收音机 是一个金矿。
Police just told me there's a third enemy element operating.
警察刚刚告诉我 第三个敌方元素正在运作。
Third element? What are you fucking talking about, Ray?
第三元素？你是什么 他妈的在说什么，雷？
We just took out three shooters.
我们刚刚击毙了三名枪手。
It's mobile, Jason.
它是移动的，杰森。
Suicide bomber headed straight for the CCP.
自杀式炸弹袭击者 直指中共。
They're targeting all the people we saved.
他们瞄准的是所有 我们拯救的人们。
All right, get Sonny and Brock back to the CCP.
好吧，叫桑尼来 布洛克回到中共。
It's obvious that we're the only ones who know how to deal
很明显，我们是 只有懂得如何处理
with a vehicle-borne IED.
带有车载简易爆炸装置 (IED)。
Okay, what about you?
好的，你呢？
Look, I got kids in here
看，我这里有孩子
and at least one more shooter. Move.
并且至少一个 更多射手。移动。
Copy.
复制。
Whoa, easy.
哇哦，很简单。
Easy. I'm your friend, I'm here to help you.
简单。我是你的朋友， 我来帮助你。
I'm gonna get you back to your dad.
我会得到你 回到你爸爸身边。
Stand up, come on.
站起来，来吧。
We're gonna get out of here. Everything's okay.
我们要离开 这儿。一切都好。
Okay...
好的...
Get in there.
进到那儿去。
- Get down! Get down! - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
- 趴下！趴下！ - 哇，哇，哇，哇，
- whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa... - Blue, blue, blue!
- 哇，哇，哇，哇，哇...... - 蓝色，蓝色，蓝色！
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
These are my friends.
这些都是我的朋友。
Struck out on the trauma kit.
创伤包被淘汰了。
Doesn't matter.
沒有關係。
When Samara wakes up, her whole world's gonna turn upside down.
当萨马拉醒来时，她的整个 世界将会天翻地覆。
Hey.
嘿。
I need you to get yourself back in the game, okay?
我需要你 回到游戏中，好吗？
I'm solid.
我很坚强。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
We got a VBIED headed straight for us right now.
我们有一个 VBIED 前往 现在就直接为我们
How far out?
有多远？
They're trying to locate its position
他们正在尝试 找到自己的位置
listening in to their comms, but let's assume close.
监听他们的通讯， 但我们假设接近。
All these people are hurt bad.
这些人都受了重伤。
I mean, anyone still at the CCP is nonambulatory.
我的意思是，还有谁 中共是不能行动的。
And we don't have time to move them.
我们没有 是时候移动它们了。
All right, on us to hold the line then.
好吧，我们来吧 那就坚持下去。
Well, I ain't ever been that good at math,
嗯，我永远不会 数学很好，
but my calculation's we're one gun short.
但我的计算 我们还差一把枪。
I write traffic tickets.
我开交通罚单。
Appreciate the trust.
感谢您的信任。
All right.
好的。
Well, some of us haven't fired a shot that counts since Mosul.
嗯，我们中的一些人还没有被解雇 这是摩苏尔战役以来至关重要的一击。
Get ready to knock that rust off.
准备敲门 除锈。
Hey, Drew.
嘿，德鲁。
We could use a hand.
我们需要帮助。
I got to get back inside.
我得回去了。
Definitely not a team guy.
绝对不是一个有团队精神的人。
They're all sitting ducks out here.
他们都坐着 鸭子在这儿。
So let's put a force field around them.
所以让我们施加力量 他们周围的田野。
Come on, let's move.
来吧，我们行动起来。
Not exactly impenetrable.
并非完全坚不可摧。
We got to stack three more cars to be fully shields up.
我们要再堆三个 汽车得到全面保护。
- All right. - Vehicle is inbound!
- 好的。 - 车辆正在驶入！
Mag check.
检查一下。
Make sure you're hot.
确保你很热。
Make your shots count!
让你的投篮有价值！
If we can't stop the car, stop the driver.
如果我们不能阻止 汽车，拦下司机。
Car's gonna make it through.
汽车将会成功通过。
On me, on me!
靠我，靠我！
Got to move, go, go! A few more feet!
得动起来，走吧， 走吧！再走几英尺！
Break off, break off! Break off!
断了，断了！断了！
Oh, please tell me that's the last of them.
噢 请告诉我 这是最后一个了。
Fuck.
他妈的。
It's over.
结束了。
The assault team's moving in.
突击队正在进驻。
As my suggestion to individually review
正如我的建议 个别审查
potential joint operations met some resistance yesterday,
潜在的联合行动 昨天遇到了一些阻力，
I'd like for us to walk through one together,
我希望我们能一起走 通过一个共同体，
get a feel for the boxes that Naval Special Warfare
感受一下盒子 海军特种作战
wants checked before signing on as a partner force.
签字前要检查 以合作伙伴的力量。
Box one: is it an appropriate use of Tier One assets,
方框一：是否合适 使用一级资产，
the most lethal weapons we have against terrorists?
我们最致命的武器 有什么措施打击恐怖分子？
That's a fair question, Lieutenant Commander.
这个问题问得很对， 少尉司令。
One of many that we need to be asking as SOCOM tries to balance
我们需要成为 特种作战司令部试图平衡
boots-on-the-ground counterterrorism actions
实地部队 反恐行动
with state-level adversary deterrence efforts.
与国家级对手 威慑力度。
All due respect, Lieutenant Davis,
恕我直言， 戴维斯中尉，
you're the only one in this room who's never actually been
你是这里唯一的人 从未真正去过的房间
boots on the ground fighting terrorists.
实地考察 打击恐怖分子。
Well, if we're trading battle scars,
好吧，如果我们 交换战争伤痕，
I took a rifle butt to the head from Venezuelan Special Police,
我的头被枪托顶着 来自委内瑞拉特别警察部队，
but I'd rather stay focused on the task at hand, sir.
但我宁愿保持专注 继续执行手头上的任务吧，先生。
The ATF is disrupting arms trafficking in the Caribbean.
ATF 正在扰乱武器 加勒比地区的贩运活动。
Pretty sure Admiral Rivas said we're worried about
非常确定 海军上将里瓦斯 说我们担心
Russia, China, Iran.
俄罗斯、中国、伊朗。
The transnational criminal organizations
跨国 犯罪组织
that are trafficking arms in the Caribbean
贩卖人口 加勒比地区的武器
are disrupting and disabling America's backyard,
正在破坏和禁用 美国的后院，
providing those nations with an opportunity to infiltrate...
为这些国家提供 一个渗透的机会……
Sorry to interrupt, but I need our ops officer.
抱歉打扰，但是 我需要我们的行动官。
Seems Bravo Team disrupted a terrorist attack.
看来 Bravo 团队被打乱了 恐怖袭击。
Terrorist attack? In Sweden?
恐怖袭击？发生在瑞典？
We don't have all the details yet,
我们没有全部 细节尚未公布，
but sounds like authorities there
但听起来 那里的当局
were completely unprepared for something of this scale.
完全没有准备 对于这种规模的事情。
It's a good thing our door-kickers were there.
这是一件好事，我们的 有破门者在那里。
A reminder...
提醒一下...
of what we do best.
我们最擅长的事情。
Well, I won't pretend I'm sorry we're heading home early.
好吧，我不会假装我是 抱歉，我们要早点回家了。
That was definitely the worst FID I ever been on.
那绝对是 我经历过的最糟糕的 FID。
Issues are usually boredom and bad food,
问题通常是 无聊和糟糕的食物，
not a group of murderous ultranationalists.
不是一群杀人犯 极端民族主义者。
Is that who they were?
他们就是这样的人吗？
Forgot to ask them before shooting them.
忘了问他们 然后再射击他们。
Yeah, the news had a statement claiming responsibility.
是的，新闻里有声明 声称对此负责。
"Making a stand for the...
“为……挺身而出”
untainted heritage of their motherland."
未受污染的遗产 他们的祖国”。
A stand that got them wrecked after losing a five-gun lead?
让他们崩溃的摊位 在失去五枪领先优势之后？
- Right? - Yeah.
- 正确的？ - 是的。
Bravo for the win.
为胜利干杯！
Still feels like we could've done more.
仍然感觉像我们 可以做得更多。
Hey.
嘿。
You saved that woman's daughter, man.
你保存了 女人的女儿，男人。
You granted her dying wish.
你满足了她临终的愿望。
There's nothing more you could've done.
再也没有了 你本可以做到的。
Okay?
好的？
Yeah.
是的。
Think Command bringing us home means
思考指挥 带我们回家意味着
they're putting us back in the fight?
他们让我们 重返战场？
I mean, come on. What else they gonna do?
我的意思是，拜托。什么 他们还能做什么？
After we pulled that off, yeah?
在我们完成这件事之后，是吗？
Especially you, Pep.
特别是你，佩普。
Hey, Pep, yeah, yeah, right.
嘿，佩普，是的，是的，对的。
Yeah? Well, I'll tell you what, Pep.
嗯？那我就 告诉你吧，佩普。
Old Yeller... well, it makes me sadder than spilt bourbon.
老黄狗......嗯，这让 让我比洒出的波旁威士忌更伤心。
Uh, definitely, uh,
嗯，当然，嗯，
all played our parts.
我们都发挥了自己的作用。
What do you say, Drew?
你说什么，德鲁？
Yeah?
是的？
How'd it feel to be babysat by Bravo 1?
感觉如何 由 Bravo 1 照顾？
Huh?
嗯？
Well, actually, it was the other way around,
嗯，事实上， 反过来，
since you asked.
既然你问了。
- The hell you talking about? - Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- 你到底在说什么？ - 嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Don't encourage this huckster, Ray.
不要鼓励 这个骗子，雷。
Just wait till Jace gets in earshot
等到杰斯 在听力范围内
and slaps his lying mouth.
并打断他撒谎的嘴。
Well, Tango had the drop on him.
好吧，Tango 抢先了一步。
I hit his light switch with one 40-yard shot.
我按了他的电灯开关 一记 40 码远的射门。
Oh, that's such bullshit.
噢，这真是胡说八道。
There's no way in hell you can make a shot
根本没有办法 你可以拍摄
like that with a pistol.
就像手枪那样。
Well, maybe you can't.
嗯，也许你不能。
Oh, so the tale about you forging your score
哦，那么关于 你伪造了你的分数
at a sniper contest is one rumor we can cross out?
在狙击比赛中 谣言我们能消除吗？
No, that happened.
不，确实发生了这样的事。
Oh, you ain't cheating,
噢，你没有作弊，
you ain't trying, boys.
你们根本就没努力，孩子们。
Well, I just got off the phone with Command.
嗯，我刚下车 用 Command 控制电话。
- Yeah? - They gonna plan a parade for us? Shit.
- 是的？ - 他们会为我们策划一场游行吗？该死。
Ah, they think that, uh, we compromised our presence
啊，他们认为，呃， 我们损害了我们的存在
by running into the fire.
冲进火里。
They can't expect us to sit on our hands
他们不能指望我们 坐在我们的手上
- while people are dying around us. - Really don't
——而我们周围却有人死去。 - 真的不知道
know what the fuck they expect from us anymore.
知道他们他妈的 对我们不再有任何期待。
But what I do know is that our shore duty continues.
但我知道的是 我们的岸上职责仍在继续。
Hey, guys, look,
嘿，伙计们，看，
remember,
记住，
w-we didn't help out back there
我们没帮上什么忙
to get in Command's good graces, okay?
进入指挥部 谢谢你，好吗？
All right, we did it to save lives.
好吧，我们做到了 它可以拯救生命。
We did it because it was the right thing to do.
我们这样做是因为 正确的事。
Yeah, best we could, anyway.
是的，无论如何我们尽力而为。
It's crazy how I was relieved
我感到如释重负，真是疯狂
when the VBIED came in and I had a target.
当 VBIED 来的时候 我有一个目标。
It's pretty twisted that it takes more of an emotional toll
这很扭曲 造成更大的情感损失
to help people than... to kill 'em.
帮助人们 而不是...杀死他们。
Bravo okay? All coming home in one piece?
太棒了，好吗？全部来了 家里还安好吗？
Yeah, they may be the problem child of DEVGRU,
是的，他们可能是 DEVGRU的问题儿童，
but Bravo knows how to win.
但 Bravo 知道如何取胜。
Well, hope this gets Command back on their side.
好吧，希望这能 指挥部回到他们那边。
Actually, I'd like to get Command on my side.
其实我想 获得我方指挥权。
Are you saying DEVGRU's resistant to change?
你是说 DEVGRU 的 抗拒改变？
Well, they all nodded
好吧，他们都点了点头
when Admiral Rivas explained the strategy.
当海军上将里瓦斯 解释了该策略。
Didn't make me think I'd get pushback every step of the way.
没想到我会得到 每一步都受到阻拦。
Yeah, I feel like there's a metaphor
是的，我觉得 有一个比喻
about trying to turn an aircraft carrier that's apt here.
关于尝试转动飞机 适合此处的运营商。
I wish it were just that.
我希望只是这样。
This feels personal.
这给人一种很私人的感觉。
Like, "You don't have a Trident. Who let you speak?"
比如，“你没有 “三叉戟。谁让你说话的？”
Well, there's a good chance you're right.
嗯，有一个很好的 也许你是对的。
But if they're not willing to work with you,
但如果他们没有 愿意与您合作，
what's to stop you from carrying out the assignment yourself?
什么阻止你携带 自己完成作业吗？
Rivas gave it to you for a reason.
里瓦斯给了 你有原因。
So you bailed on the VBIED
所以你放弃了 VBIED
'cause you were looking out for Jace, huh?
因为你在看 去找 Jace 吧？
No man left behind's a tenet
不抛弃任何人的原则
even a lone wolf like me believes in.
即使是一匹孤狼 像我一样相信。
Maybe you're a team guy after all.
也许你是一个 毕竟是团队成员。
Or maybe I'm just looking to get home
或者也许我只是 想回家
to torch tax dollars on my next Pro Dev trip.
烧掉税金 我的下一次 Pro Dev 之旅。
Oh, and anyway, you know you can't be a team guy
哦，无论如何，你知道 你不能成为一个团队合作者
if... there is no team, right?
如果……没有队伍的话，对吧？
Just take the damn beer, dickface.
就拿该死的 啤酒，混蛋脸。
Oh, go ahead and drink both of 'em.
哦，继续吧 把它们都喝掉。
It sounds like this might be
听起来这可能是
the last time Bravo tastes victory.
最后一次 Bravo 尝到了胜利的滋味。
Oh, God. Okay.
哦天啊。好的。
Hey, hey, I don't know what to say.
嘿，嘿，我不知道 知道该说什么。
This guy.
这家伙。
Hey, hold up.
嘿，稍等一下。
You say something?
你说句话？
Well, I know you... you wanted
嗯，我了解你...你想要
to get your little girl one of these.
得到你的小 女孩，其中之一。
You take it.
你拿着。
You know, I can't accept a... dime piece
你知道，我不能 接受一枚......一角硬币
from a... a douchebag.
来自一个......混蛋。
It's real.
这是真的。
After that shit was over,
那些事结束后，
I-I swiped it at the mall.
我在商场刷了它。
Along with six more.
还有另外六个。
Just keep it.
保留它。
So close to home, and you still look like
离家这么近，而且 你看起来还是像
you're a million miles away.
你离我有百万英里远。
Yeah. Yeah, I didn't expect to be back
是的，我没有 希望回来
on the crazy train so soon, you know?
在疯狂的火车上 这么快，你知道吗？
Tell me about it.
跟我说说看。
Thought I was cruising into retirement, and, uh,
我以为我在巡航 退休后，呃
next thing I know, I'm doing E.R. under fire.
我知道的下一件事就是我 在压力之下做急诊室工作。
Now, you didn't keep me outside, uh,
现在，你没有 把我挡在外面，呃，
'cause I'm at the one-yard line on my retirement, did you?
因为我在一码处 您对我的退休有什么看法？
What? No.
啥？不。
- Classic Bravo 1, if so. - No, no.
- 如果是这样的话，那就是经典的 Bravo 1。 - 不，不。
No way. It's just...
没办法。只是……
Just, uh, everything happened so fast,
一切 发生得如此之快，
felt more like my first op than my last.
感觉更像我的 这是我第一次做手术，而不是最后一次。
Part of you wish you had stuck to triage with me,
你内心深处希望自己能 坚持和我一起分诊，
kept your ass out of the fight?
你怎么不参与战斗？
What's that mean?
那是什么意思？
I heard you had a close call
我听说你差点出事了
Drew sniped you out of.
德鲁将你击败了。
Not how it went down?
情况不是这样吗？
Guy had me dead to rights.
这家伙把我彻底打败了。
That'll rattle anybody.
这会让任何人感到不安。
Yeah, yeah. That close call spun me out for a minute, I guess.
是的，是的。那次险些发生的事 我想，让我出去一会儿。
You'll shake it off.
你会摆脱它的。
Nothing you haven't done a hundred times before.
你没有做过的事 以前一百次了。
It was such a nice surprise hearing from you.
这真是太好了 很惊讶收到你的来信。
So, your, um... your new post in Acquisition and Sustainment
那么，你的新帖子 在采购和维护方面
includes weekend work in Vah Beach?
包括周末 在 Vah Beach 工作吗？
This trip is strictly social.
这次旅行纯粹是社交旅行。
Speaking of new jobs, how's yours?
说到新 工作，你的工作还好吗？
Let's just say that it's making me nostalgic
这么说吧 这让我很怀旧
for some of our old arguments.
对于我们的一些旧论点。
Funny to think we were on opposite sides
有趣的是，我们 站在对立面
of a policy debate and somehow both wrong.
政策辩论和 不知何故，两者都错了。
Integrated deterrence feels like the right compromise.
综合威慑感 就像正确的妥协。
You want to tell my coworkers that?
你想告诉 我的同事那？
If they're like me, they're more afraid of you
如果他们像我一样， 他们更怕你
than you are of them.
比你更了解他们。
But you need a favor, I'm your guy.
但你需要 恩，我是你的男人。
Well, thank you. I will keep that in mind.
嗯，谢谢你。我 我会记住这一点。
Actually, one of the reasons I reached out.
事实上， 我伸出援手的原因。
I need a favor.
我需要帮忙。
Uh, you remember that file I got you about an ODA tic in Mali?
呃，你记得我拿到的那个文件吗 您了解马里的官方发展援助 (ODA) 吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Army CID's investigating an assault
陆军刑事侦缉处 调查袭击事件
on the battlespace commander.
战场指挥官。
- Colonel Decker? - He's a general now.
— 德克尔上校？ - 他现在是一名将军。
But, yeah. Apparently, the assailant was looking
但是，是的。显然， 袭击者当时正在
for payback for a security failure, so,
为了回报 安全故障，因此，
CID's looking into all actions he was involved in,
CID 正在调查所有 他参与的行为，
going through with a fine-toothed comb,
经历 一把密齿梳子，
see if anybody had a beef with him.
看看是否有人 对他有意见。
Do you think there's something in that file?
你认为 该文件中有什么东西吗？
I don't know. The man's served for almost two decades.
我不知道。这个男人的 任职近二十年。
Just trying to cover my own ass.
我只是想掩饰我自己。
Look, I doubt CID will ask you about a file
看，我怀疑 CID 会 询问你关于文件的问题
you requested through proper channels,
您请求通过 适当的渠道，
but if they do, you mind
但如果他们这么做了，你介意
not mentioning that you were dissatisfied with the results
没提到你 对结果不满意
and I cut some red tape for you?
我可以帮你省去一些繁琐手续吗？
My lips are sealed.
我守口如瓶。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Definitely prefer this reintegration routine
绝对喜欢这个 重返社会常规
to burritos.
墨西哥卷饼。
Well, okay, burritos don't apply, okay?
好吧，墨西哥卷饼 别申请，好吗？
FID was not a mission.
FID 不是一项使命。
What?! What?
啥？！啥？
Putting down an extremist attack doesn't qualify as an op?
镇压极端分子 攻击不算作操作吗？
Well, let's just say that, uh, we got lucky, you know?
好吧，这么说吧， 呃，我们很幸运，你知道吗？
- Right place, right time. - Lucky?
- 正确的地点，正确的时间。 - 幸运的？
Most action you've seen lately was on that trip
你见过的最精彩的动作 最近在那次旅行中
through Central Virginia's wine country.
通过中央 弗吉尼亚州的葡萄酒之乡。
Yeah, and what did I end up with? Beer-of-the-month club.
是啊，我最后怎么样了 和？月度啤酒俱乐部。
Should have just gotten the T-shirt.
应该 拿到了T恤。
So it wasn't rough, then,
所以这并不困难，
getting thrown back in
被扔回
and having to switch gears so quickly?
并且必须切换 齿轮这么快？
Was like riding a bike.
就像骑自行车一样。
It was. I'll tell you what.
是的。我来告诉你吧。
- Let's get back into... - Mmm.
- 让我们回到... - 嗯。
This reintegration process, shall we?
重新融入 过程，我们可以吗？
Oh!
哦！
Cerby, bed. Go to bed. Bed.
瑟比，睡觉。去睡觉。睡觉。
Saved hundreds of innocent lives, and yet
拯救了数百 无辜的生命，然而
we are back to doggy day care.
我们又回到了狗狗日托中心。
Well, I hate to admit it,
嗯，我不愿意承认，
but after that close call with the VBIED...
但在那之后 与 VBIED 通话...
a few more weeks of briefcase duty doesn't sound so bad.
再过几个星期的公文包 职责听起来并不是那么糟糕。
You guys up for hitting the Bulkhead?
你们 撞到舱壁了？
Wish I could, but, uh,
我希望可以，但是，呃，
I should get home.
我该回家了。
Yeah.
是的。
I get the urge to hold your babies
我有冲动 抱抱你的宝宝
after what we went through.
在我们经历了这些之后。
I've gotten so used to, uh,
我已经习惯了，呃，
what the future with them's gonna be like,
未来会怎样 他们会像
I almost forgot that war likes to have the last word.
我几乎忘记了那场战争 喜欢说最后一句话。
You boys have fun.
你们玩得开心。
- Later, Ray. - All right, buddy.
- 稍后，雷。 - 好的，伙计。
And then there were two... unless
然后 是两个……除非
- you want to call Brock? - Yeah.
- 你想给布洛克打电话吗？ - 是的。
Nah, you and the Radio City Brockettes
不，你和 无线电城布洛克特
are on your own.
靠你自己。
See, I have to, uh, FaceTime Leanne,
瞧，我必须…… FaceTime Leanne，
make sure that, uh, she ain't calling anybody else Daddy.
确保她不会 叫别人爸爸。
Then I got to call Stella.
然后我给斯特拉打电话。
Oh, give her the good news, we got pulled back early,
哦，告诉她这个好消息， 我们提前被撤退了，
and you can go support her at Ben's hearing?
你可以去支持 她会出席本的听证会吗？
Uh, no, there's actually a change of plans.
呃，不，实际上有 计划改变。
She had to head back to her folks'
她必须前往 回到父母身边
and help her pops recover from knee surgery,
并帮助她爸爸康复 从膝盖手术开始，
so she ended up just sending his lawyer a letter.
所以她最后只是 给他的律师发了一封信。
- Well, you're off the hook. - Yeah.
- 好了，你已经摆脱困境了。 - 是的。
It's probably best that way.
或许这样才是最好的。
You know, I'd rather eat a bug than see Ben right now.
你知道，我宁愿吃 比现在见到 Ben 更糟糕。
I thought you didn't blame him?
我以为你不会责怪他吗？
All I know is, Clay's gone.
我只知道，克莱已经走了。
You know, between the shore duty
你知道，在岸上值班期间
and Drew's doomsaying,
以及德鲁的悲观预言，
uh, I just feel like
呃，我只是觉得
Bravo is slipping in the rearview.
Bravo 正在下滑 在后视镜中。
Oh, don't let Drew get in your head.
哦，别让德鲁 进入你的脑海。
Even if he was on the level,
即使他水平不错，
you've got to wonder about a team guy
你一定会好奇 关于一个团队成员
who doesn't want teammates.
谁不想要队友呢。
Yeah. Clay always said, "We all need teammates."
是的。克莱总是说， “我们都需要队友。”
He was right.
他是对的。
Man was not meant to tarry alone.
人类本不该 独自逗留。
What the hell's that mean?
这到底是什么意思？
Ah, it's just that, seems like
啊，只是，好像
Clay walked that talk even outside the teams.
克莱言出必行 甚至在球队之外。
Like what he was trying to do for Ben?
就像他 想为本做些什么？
What the fuck?
这他妈的是什么？
Sorry.
对不起。
Are you all right?
你还好吗？
It's been months since you had a night terror.
已经过去好几个月了 你做噩梦了。
No, I'm all right. I'm good. I'm good.
不，我很好。 我很好。我很好。
No. No, clearly you're not.
不，不，显然你不是。
It was just a dream. It was just a bad dream.
那只是一场梦。 只是一场噩梦。
I'm good. Just go back to bed, all right?
我很好。回去吧 去睡觉吧？
Hope everyone had a good weekend.
希望每个人都能 愉快的周末。
Lieutenant Commander Kirkpatrick,
少校 柯克帕特里克，
you're back. So this means you've set aside your doubts
你回来了。这意味着 你已经放下了疑虑
about my fitness to lead this initiative
关于我的健康状况 领导这一倡议
or about the initiative itself.
或有关该倡议本身。
Or you know how important this is to Admiral Rivas
或者你知道这有多重要 这是给海军上将里瓦斯的
and don't want to run afoul of him.
也不想 与他发生冲突。
Well, you don't rise as quickly as you did
那你就别想起来 和你一样快
without understanding politics.
不懂政治。
Great. So let's talk politics.
太好了。那我们来谈谈政治吧。
I get that you all think we're wasting our time.
我明白你们都认为 我们正在浪费时间。
But here's the thing...
但事情是这样的...
SOCOM gave us one job to do,
SOCOM 给了我们一项任务，
find a joint op with an external partner.
找到一个联合行动 外部合作伙伴。
We don't do that,
我们不会这么做，
it makes it that much harder for Captain Walch
这使得它如此之多 对沃尔奇上尉来说更加困难
to fight for DEVGRU's share of the pie.
为 DEVGRU 而战 份额。
I'm not willing to let that happen.
我不愿意 让那件事发生。
So I'm picking an op, with or without you.
所以我选了一个操作， 不管有没有你。
If it matters, I'm a person that shares credit for success
如果这很重要，我是一个人 分享成功的功劳
and takes full blame for failure.
并充分利用 失败的责任。
I understand your client would like
我理解你的 客户会喜欢
to make a statement before I deliver my ruling.
发表声明 我宣告我的裁决。
Mr. Gossett,
格塞特先生，
you may proceed.
你可以继续。
Just wanted to say I am...
我只是想说我……
really sorry for everything that happened that night.
真的很抱歉 那是那天晚上发生的事。
Someone tried to... help me,
有人试图……帮助我，
save me, really.
救救我吧，真的。
Paid the ultimate price for it.
为此付出了终极的代价。
So, whatever the court sees fit...
因此，无论 法庭认为合适……
I deserve it.
我应得的。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Does anyone else want to speak on Mr. Gossett's behalf?
还有人想 您能代表戈塞特先生发言吗？
If there's no further comment,
如果没有其他评论，
we'll continue with sentencing.
我们将继续宣判。
To the charge of felony vandalism...
指控 重罪破坏……
Your Honor.
启禀大人。
My name is Sonny Quinn.
我的名字是桑尼·奎因。
Clay Spenser,
克莱·斯宾塞，
the man Mr. Gossett credits to saving him...
格塞特先生 感谢你们拯救了他……
he was my friend.
他是我的朋友。
May I speak?
我可以讲话吗？
You may proceed.
您可以继续。
Clay was the best friend I ever had.
粘土是最好的 我曾经有过的朋友。
And I can't help but stand here...
我无能为力 但站在这里……
and look at Ben...
看看本……
part of me wants to tear him limb from limb.
我的一部分想要 把他撕成碎片。
But Clay, he...
但是克莱，他……
he was a better man than I ever dreamed of being.
他比 我曾梦想过。
And he'd never blame Ben for any of this.
他从不责怪 对这一切，本表示感谢。
Both Ben and I,
本和我
we lost our best teammate that terrible night.
我们失去了最好的队友 那个可怕的夜晚。
So it is...
原来如此...
it is on me...
这是我的错……
to be the next man up.
成为下一个崛起的人。
I'm asking the court to...
我请求法庭...
to give Ben a second chance
给本第二次机会
at having a good life.
过上好日子。
Because I know in my heart that, uh...
因为我知道 我的心那，呃……
well, Clay...
好吧，克莱……
he'd think he deserved it.
他会认为这是他应得的。
So I do, too.
我也是这么认为。
So right back into pushing papers, huh?
所以回到 推销文件，嗯？
Yeah.
是的。
This is one packet I don't mind pushing.
这是一个包 不介意推一下。
- It's my retirement docs. - Yeah?
- 这是我的退休文件。 - 是的？
- Making it official right now. - That's hard to believe.
- 立即正式宣布。 - 这真令人难以置信。
20 years of warfighting fits
20 年的战斗经历
all into that one little single folder.
全部投入到那一个 小單個文件夾。
That's quite a career, brother.
这可真是一份了不起的职业，兄弟。
So you, uh... are you here to, um, deliver the smackdown
那么你，呃...你在这里吗 嗯，给予打击
to Command for not reinstating you and Bravo?
命令不 恢复你和 Bravo 的职务？
I mean, I might stick around to watch you crack some skulls,
我的意思是我可能会留下来 看着你敲碎一些人的头骨，
rearrange some furniture.
重新布置一些家具。
See, man, I knew a little taste of action
瞧，伙计，我知道一个 行动的滋味
would snap you right back into battle mode.
会让你正确 重新进入战斗模式。
No, I'm not that guy anymore, man.
不，我不是那样 再也不是那个男人了，哥们。
I'm just here to do my shore duty.
我来这里只是为了 履行我的岸上职责。
Whatever the brass decides to do with Bravo,
无论黄铜 决定和 Bravo 合作，
I'm good with it.
我对此很满意。
Wow.
哇。
Jason Hayes giving peace a chance.
杰森·海耶斯 和平的机会。
You know what?
你知道吗？
All the work you've put in on yourself...
你所做的一切 投入到你自己身上……
I'm proud of you for how far you've come.
我为你感到骄傲 你已经走了多远。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, man, just being in that courtroom,
是的，哥们，只是 在那个法庭里，
I-I don't know what came over me.
我不知道 我怎么了。
I just got up and started talking.
我刚起床 开始讲话。
A door-kicking Atticus Finch.
踢门的阿提克斯·芬奇。
Whatever Batman villain that may be.
无论蝙蝠侠 或许是个恶棍。
Hey, but seeing Ben up there, alone,
嘿，但是看到本 独自一人在那里，
not even fighting for himself,
甚至不为自己而战，
yeah, I knew Clay wouldn't want that.
是的，我认识 Clay 我不想要那样。
You did good.
你做得很好。
Clay was there with you, spurring you on.
克莱在那里 你，激励你。
Yeah.
是的。
Ah, from a pat on the back chased by a pain in my ass.
啊，拍拍肩膀 被屁股上的疼痛所追赶。
You invite this guy?
你邀请这个人吗？
No.
不。
But after what we went through together,
但之后我们 一起经历过，
- he can pull up a seat. - I doubt he will.
- 他可以拉把椅子过来。 - 我怀疑他会这么做。
That grifter's probably here to scam drunks or...
那个骗子可能 来这里是为了欺骗醉汉或者......
steal quarters from the phone booth.
偷窃 电话亭。
Drew.
德鲁。
Yo, grab a glass.
哟，拿一杯。
It's Brock's tab.
这是布洛克的标签。
There it is.
就在那儿。
That's why you keep him around.
这就是你让他留在你身边的原因。
Nobody talks about Brock like that.
没人谈论 布洛克就是这样的。
Well, except us.
嗯，除了我们。
Why don't you pull up a chair, big guy,
你为什么不拉 坐上椅子，大个子，
- take a load off. - I'm good.
- 减轻负担。 - 我很好。
Don't want to interrupt Throuples Night.
不想打扰 三人行之夜。
A SEAL that hates SEALs telling jokes
憎恨的海豹突击队员 海豹突击队员讲笑话
that hate laughter.
讨厌笑声的人。
That's awesome. Awesome.
太棒了，太棒了。
You enjoy yourselves, boys.
你们玩得开心吧，孩子们。
Huh?
嗯？
The guy is unbelievable.
这家伙真是令人难以置信。
Told you he wouldn't sit with us.
告诉你他不会 和我们坐在一起。
All this proves is another rumor.
这一切都证明 又一个谣言。
Falls for every woman he sees.
爱上他所见到的每个女人。
So what's so important that you'd step into a dump like this
那么什么才是最重要的 你会走进这样的垃圾场
instead of just telling me over the phone?
而不是仅仅告诉 打电话给我吗？
We have a situation.
我们遇到了一种情况。
Sounds ominous.
听起来很不祥。
Leo can't make it to your party in Saint-Tropez?
Leo 不能参加你的 在圣特罗佩参加派对？
Cute.
可爱的。
Actually,
实际上，
the family needs us to circle the wagons.
家庭需要我们 把马车围成一圈。
Remind the, uh... the council of deadbeats
提醒一下，呃…… 懒汉委员会
I'm not really into family favors.
我不是真的 成为家庭的恩惠。
Go ahead. Ice me out.
来吧。冰冻我。
Dad, too.
爸爸也一样。
But this could be your reputation on the line.
但这可能是你的 名誉受损。
God forbid.
但愿不会。
How will I ever show my face in the vineyard again?
我将如何展现我的 又在葡萄园里露面了？
There's a reporter doing a podcast
有一位记者 做播客
about "the House of Franklin."
关于“富兰克林之家”。
- Mm. - She's digging into the whole family saga...
- 毫米。 - 她正在深入调查整个家族的传奇故事……
ancestors, right up to now.
祖宗，至今。
She's relentless.
她很执着。
Does not hold back.
毫不保留。
Now, you realize our family's a joke,
现在你意识到 我们家就是个笑话，
right, Nora?
对吧，诺拉？
A sex tape away from being the Hiltons.
远离性爱录像带 是希尔顿夫妇。
I still say you have it in you, sis.
我还是说你 你有这个能力，姐妹。
Okay. Despite this "salt of the earth" metamorphosis,
好吧。尽管这个“盐的 地球”的蜕变，
you're still an asshole.
你还是一个混蛋。
Maybe if you guys ever got your hands dirty,
也许如果你们曾经 弄脏了你的手，
you'd realize there's no reason to cry
你会意识到 没有理由哭泣
over a little spilled tea.
洒出的一点茶水。
We can only aspire to be like you
我们只能渴望 像你一样
and have so very little to lose.
而且几乎没有什么可失去的。
Until then,
到那时为止，
if and when you're contacted by her,
如果你 她联系了
help us out and do what you do best...
帮助我们 你最擅长做什么……
don't play ball.
不要玩球。
Wow. Whoa.
哇喔。哇喔。
- Hey. - What's, uh, what's all this?
- 嘿。 - 呃，这都是些什么？
The Zillow listings you sent me
你发给我的 Zillow 列表
- when I was in Afghanistan. - Right.
- 当我在阿富汗的时候。 - 正确的。
I found a few more.
我又找到了一些。
- Mm. - Thought we could...
- 毫米。 - 我以为我们可以……
discuss them over extra cheese...
讨论它们 额外的奶酪……
- Right. - Pick some,
- 正确的。 - 挑选一些，
maybe go check 'em out this weekend?
也许去看看 这周末出去玩吗？
Second thoughts already?
已经开始重新考虑了吗？
Uh...
呃…
No. No, it's-it's, uh...
不，不，这，这，呃……
it's not about that. At all.
根本不是这个原因。
About something.
关于某事。
Um...
嗯…
The, um...
那，嗯…
attack that we had in Sweden.
我们在瑞典遭受的袭击。
It, uh...
这，呃…
It wasn't just like riding a bike.
这不仅仅是 就像骑自行车一样。
I got a little too comfortable sitting on the sidelines.
我有点太舒服了 坐在场边。
Like...
喜欢...
way comfortable.
非常舒服。
A little too much.
有点太多了。
There's no shame
没有什么可羞耻的
in enjoying a break from the blood and the trauma,
享受休息 鲜血和创伤，
life-and-death decisions.
生死攸关的决定。
I mean, it's no wonder you had a night terror.
我的意思是，这也难怪 你做噩梦了。
Yeah, well, it was...
是啊，嗯，是的......
I just put up my walls.
我刚刚筑起了墙。
Again. And...
再次。并且...
I'm sorry I lied to you.
我很抱歉我对你撒了谎。
I just...
我只是……
didn't think I was that guy anymore.
没想到我 再也没有那个家伙了。
Well, this conversation proves you aren't.
嗯，这次谈话 证明你不是。
Yeah.
是的。
It's just, like, all the work that I have done lately
这就像 我最近做的工作
on myself,
我自己，
all the TBI treatments, focusing on you,
所有 TBI 治疗， 专注于你，
focusing on my kids, I found a balance.
专注于我的孩子， 我找到了平衡点。
And I really liked it.
我真的很喜欢它。
I mean, I loved it. I...
我是说，我很喜欢它。我……
For once, I could really see...
这一次我真正地看到了……
or at least get a glimpse into the future,
或者至少得到一个 展望未来，
what that would be like.
那会是什么样的。
But, uh, after this one op,
但这次手术后，
I just feel like running back into the fire.
我只想跑步 重新投入火中。
All that's just gonna...
这一切只不过是...
destroy the progress that I've made.
破坏进步 我做的。
Everything's gonna blow up, and...
一切都会 爆炸，然后……
I'm scared about that.
我有点害怕那件事。
I really am.
我确实如此。
You've worked really hard to swing the pendulum this far.
你真的非常努力 把钟摆摆到这里。
Unlikely it'll swing back.
它不太可能会反弹。
Yeah.
是的。
You're right.
你说得对。
Right.
正确的。
Captioning sponsored by CBS
字幕由 CBS 赞助
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
媒体访问字幕 WGBH 小组 access.wgbh.org